<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv><programme start="20241102190000" stop="20241102213000" channel="10601"><title lang="ar">Franco STUPACZUK ARG Miguel YANGUAS ESP vs Javier GARRIDO ESP Lucas BERGAMINI BRA - Final Men - Prem</title><desc lang="ar">The 2024 NewGiza Premier Padel P2 takes place from October 21-27 at the NewGiza Sports Club in Egypt. With a €250,000 prize pool, it features top international male and female players competing for ranking points and glory in one of the region’s premier padel events</desc><category lang="ar">باديل</category></programme><programme start="20241102192000" stop="20241102213000" channel="10802"><title lang="ar">Hertha BSC vs FC Koln - Bundesliga 2 - 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Bundesliga 2 division is the men's second professional association football division of the German football league system. Bundesliga 2 is the ideal proving ground for younger players in Germany before stepping up to the Bundesliga, but it’s also simply a great league to watch if you want drama and excitement at a level that still boasts quality.</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني الدرجة الثانية</category></programme><programme start="20241102195500" stop="20241102220000" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">Saint-Étienne vs Strasbourg - French Ligue 1 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">St Etienne will host Strasbourg in Ligue 1 for the first time since February 20, 2022, when they drew 2-2. ASSE are unbeaten in their last five home games against RSCA in the top-flight. St Etienne have fewer than 10 points after nine games in a Ligue 1 season for the second consecutive time, a situation that had never occurred in their previous 16 seasons in the top-flight.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الفرنسي</category></programme><programme start="20241102200000" stop="20241102220000" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">Toulouse  vs St Raphael - LNH Division 1 - French Handball Starligue</title><desc lang="ar">Dive into the excitement of French handball with Liqui Moly Starligue, formerly LNH Division 1. Established in 1952, this premier league event features 16 top teams battling for glory. With Montpellier’s  14 Handball titles and Paris Saint-Germain's 11 wins, the competition is fierce. Champions earn spots in the EHF Champions League, while cup winners qualify for the European League.</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الفرنسي لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241102210000" stop="20241102212800" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">The Big Interview 2024/25 - Joe Aribo</title><desc lang="ar">Despite finishing as runners-up with Glasgow Rangers in the Europa League as well as scoring in the final, Joe Aribo decided his journey would continue away from Scotland, Instead opting for the Premier League with Southampton. This week on The Big Interview, Aribo reflects on his Nigerian roots, growing up playing football in the cages of South-East London, how he studied sports science, and how he's finding life on the south coast.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241102210000" stop="20241102231500" channel="10801"><title lang="ar">Holger RUNE (DEN) vs Alexander ZVEREV (GER)- SF1 - ATP 1000 Rolex Paris Masters 2024</title><desc lang="ar">The Rolex Paris Masters is the ninth and final ATP Masters 1000 event of the season. As the final tournament of the regular men’s tennis season, the Palais Omnisports in Bercy showcases the cream of the crop as players vie to win the prestigious title and clinch the remaining qualifying spots in the season-ending Nitto ATP Finals.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241102210000" stop="20241102230000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">L.A. Lakers vs Toronto - NBA 2024 Regular Season</title><desc lang="ar">NBA 2024 Regular Season</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الأميركي لكرة السلة</category></programme><programme start="20241102210000" stop="20241102220000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">The Issue of The Day - 2024</title><desc lang="ar">The Issue Of The Day, from the beIn Sports News Team, takes an in depth look at the the main story form the world of sport from the last 24 hours.</desc><category lang="ar">الأخبار الرياضية</category></programme><programme start="20241102210000" stop="20241102213000" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">LaLiga Power Ep.1</title><desc lang="ar">LALIGA Power is a program that pays tribute to all those who inspire the world through the values of football. In each episode, we discover the passion celebrities have for their club and experience a match day with the most dedicated fans in the world, as well as showing curiosities about LALIGA clubs and players. Because they are the strength of our football.








</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241102210000" stop="20241102224500" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Holstein Kiel vs Heidenheim - Bundesliga 2024/25 Week 9</title><desc lang="ar">Holstein Kiel are the 58th Bundesliga debutants, while 1. FC Heidenheim became the 57th last season. The Storks have lost just one their last six competitive home games against FCH, a 1-0 defeat in February 2020. The last meeting between the sides in Kiel in October 2022 finished in a 3-1 win for the hosts. With just two points from their first eight games, Holstein Kiel have made the worst start of any Bundesliga newcomer. The Storks are also the first team to concede at least two goals in each of the first eight matches in their top-flight history.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241102210000" stop="20241102213000" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">Fast Zone / 2024</title><desc lang="ar">Covering everything from prototypes to endurance racing, karting to airplanes and even some real oddities… With both tradition and a fresh take on motorsport, Fast/Zone is the ultimate resource for everything that is fast and fascinating!







































</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241102212800" stop="20241102231600" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">Luton Town vs West Brom - EFL - English Football League  - Championship 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">EFL - English Football League  - Championship 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">دوري البطولة الإنجليزية - الدرجة الأولى</category></programme><programme start="20241102213000" stop="20241103000000" channel="10802"><title lang="ar">Triathlon SuperTri  -Triathlon  Toulouse France 2024</title><desc lang="ar">The 2024 SuperTri Triathlon in Toulouse, France, brings together elite athletes for a fast-paced and thrilling competition. Athletes will push their limits across swimming, cycling, and running events on a scenic course through the heart of Toulouse. With top international triathletes participating, the event promises exciting performances and intense rivalries as they compete for victory in one of the sport's most prestigious events.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241102213000" stop="20241103031800" channel="10601"><title lang="ar">Spain vs Argentina  - Women's Final - Padel world championship Qatar 2024</title><desc lang="ar">Spain and Argentina are set to meet for the 16th time in the women’s final of the 2024 World Padel Championship in Doha, Qatar. Both teams hold an impressive record, each with 8 titles, showcasing their rivalry at the top of the sport. Spain enters the match with momentum, having won the previous five finals in a row, while Argentina looks to break this streak and reclaim the championship.</desc><category lang="ar">باديل</category></programme><programme start="20241102213000" stop="20241102220000" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">UEFA UCL Magazine 2024/2025 - MD3 Review</title><desc lang="ar">A recap of the best of the action, plus a look forward to the next Match Day in Europe’s premium football competition, the UEFA Champions League. This season is the first in the new format, with 36 participating teams in a league phase replacing the previous Group stage. All matches from the UEFA Champions League are live and exclusive only on beIN.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241102213000" stop="20241102220000" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">GP Confidential 2024 / Magazine</title><desc lang="ar">Explore the sporting secrets of F1. Across 25 episodes and in crisp 3D animations, we analyses the technical details, which decide which teams make the most of the rules - and which need to go back to the drawing board. Complemented by features on historical milestones as well as race previews - GP Confidential is the perfect treat for any F1 fan.
























</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241102220000" stop="20241102223000" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">UEFA UCL Magazine 2024/2025 - MD3 Review</title><desc lang="ar">A recap of the best of the action, plus a look forward to the next Match Day in Europe’s premium football competition, the UEFA Champions League. This season is the first in the new format, with 36 participating teams in a league phase replacing the previous Group stage. All matches from the UEFA Champions League are live and exclusive only on beIN.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241102220000" stop="20241103003000" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">Boston Celtics vs Charlotte Hornets - NBA 2024 Regular Season</title><desc lang="ar">NBA 2024 Regular Season</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الأميركي لكرة السلة</category></programme><programme start="20241102220000" stop="20241102222900" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">LaLiga Talking Football 2024/2025 Ep.1</title><desc lang="ar">TALKING FOOTBALL is an exclusive unique window into Spanish football and the people that have made it what it is. We dress as coaches and join their meetings and private discussions. We talk to LALIGA legends in their environment about deep issues, their successes but also their weaknesses. We'd like to lead the media agenda with conversations that you don't normally hear with managers, players and the most recognisable directors. All that presented by Guillem Balague.








</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241102220000" stop="20241102230000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Al Hassad</title><desc lang="ar">Al Hassad is a nighltly studio from beIN Sports News that looks at the stories that have made the headlines in the world of sport and those stories that will be making the headlines tomorrow morning.</desc><category lang="ar">الأخبار الرياضية</category></programme><programme start="20241102220000" stop="20241102223000" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">QSL 2024/2025 Best Goals of QSL 2024/2025</title><desc lang="ar">The best goals from different rounds of Qatar Football league.</desc><category lang="ar">دوري نجوم قطر</category></programme><programme start="20241102222900" stop="20241103001800" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">Osasuna vs Real Valladolid - LaLiga 2024/2025 Week 12</title><desc lang="ar">Osasuna have lost just one of their last nine matches against Real Valladolid in LaLiga although five of those ended in draws  – only against Athletic  and Valencia  have they had more draws in the top-flight than against them. At home, Osasuna have lost just one of their last 16 games against Real Valladolid in LaLiga  and have kept a clean sheet in each of their last four, their longest run without conceding at home to the Castilians in the top-flight.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإسباني لكرة القدم</category></programme><programme start="20241102223000" stop="20241103001500" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">Al Wakrah vs Um Salal - Qatar League 2024/25 - MD9</title><desc lang="ar">Qatar League 2024/25 - MD9</desc><category lang="ar">دوري نجوم قطر</category></programme><programme start="20241102223000" stop="20241103001600" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">Lille vs Olympique Lyonnais - French Ligue 1 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Lille lost their last game against Lyon in Ligue 1  but have not recorded two consecutive defeats against OL in the top-flight since the 2006-07 season. Lille have won only one of their last eight Ligue 1 games against Lyon, winning 1-0 in March 2020.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الفرنسي</category></programme><programme start="20241102224500" stop="20241103003000" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Hoffenheim vs St. Pauli - Bundesliga 2024/25 Week 9</title><desc lang="ar">Both of TSG Hoffenheim’s home games against FC St. Pauli have ended in draws: 1-1 in the second division in 2007/08 and 2-2 in the Bundesliga in 2010/11. The two sides teams have each won in Hamburg, meaning their head-to-head record is even after four competitive meetings. TSG are still unbeaten against St. Pauli in the top flight. TSG Hoffenheim have won just one of their last seven Bundesliga matches, a 3-1 victory over Bochum in their last home game. Hoffenheim’s current tally of eight points after eight matchdays has only been worse in the top flight in 2015/16. However, TSG are unbeaten in three games  after previously suffering four straight defeats.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241102230000" stop="20241102231500" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Al Jawla  - Live Studio @02:00</title><desc lang="ar">Al Jawla covers the latest news and stories from sporting events across the planet. Including latest results and latest scores from the most recent games taking place. This daily look at the latest stories provides a fast paced update to sporting events.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241102230000" stop="20241102233000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">EPL Stories  2024/2025 - Emmanuel Adebayor</title><desc lang="ar">Stories explores Emmanuel Adebayor's extraordinary life and Premier League career with Arsenal, Manchester City, Tottenham and Crystal Palace, to surviving the Togo bus attack in 2010. We delve into his rise as one of Africa's finest football talents and how the near-death experience shaped his resilience and outlook beyond football</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241102231500" stop="20241102233000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">beIN Experiments - News</title><desc lang="ar">One of beIN's many  reporters chooses a sport to try and master. In each episode there is a chance to experience the challenges faced in different sports from different parts of the world .</desc><category lang="ar">الأخبار الرياضية</category></programme><programme start="20241102231500" stop="20241103023000" channel="10801"><title lang="ar">Karen KHACHANOV vs Ugo HUMBERT (FRA)- SF2 - ATP 1000 Rolex Paris Masters 2024</title><desc lang="ar">The Rolex Paris Masters is the ninth and final ATP Masters 1000 event of the season. As the final tournament of the regular men’s tennis season, the Palais Omnisports in Bercy showcases the cream of the crop as players vie to win the prestigious title and clinch the remaining qualifying spots in the season-ending Nitto ATP Finals.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241102231600" stop="20241103010300" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">AFC Bournemouth vs Manchester City - English Premier League 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Bournemouth have won none of their 20 league games against Man City. It’s the most one side has faced another without ever winning in English Football League history. Manchester City have won all 14 of their Premier League games against Bournemouth by an aggregate score of 45-7. It’s the best 100% record any team has against another in English top-flight history.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإنجليزي الممتاز</category></programme><programme start="20241102233000" stop="20241103000000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">La Liga Chronicles 2024/25 Ep.9</title><desc lang="ar">"A look back at the standout games from the most recent matchday, through extensive highlights and spectacularfootage."



































</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241102233000" stop="20241103000000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">Preston vs Arsenal - Mini Match - Carabao Cup 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Preston vs Arsenal - Extended Highlights - Carabao Cup 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">مباريات قصيرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103000000" stop="20241103003000" channel="10802"><title lang="ar">HL - High Diving World Cup 2024 – Womens</title><desc lang="ar">The world's top-ranked men's and women's high diving from 27m and 20m competed to make impressive strides in the Bahrain round to qualify for the 2025 World Championships in Singapore.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103000000" stop="20241103003000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">News Bulletin - Live Studio @03:00</title><desc lang="ar">Latest news from the beIn SPORTS News room, previewing and reviewing developments and scores with contribution from around the world from beIN's reporters.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103000000" stop="20241103003000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">Tottenham vs Man City - Mini Match - Carabao Cup 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Tottenham vs Man City - Extended Highlights - Carabao Cup 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">مباريات قصيرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103001500" stop="20241103020000" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">Al Gharafa vs Al Arabi - Qatar League 2024/25 - MD9</title><desc lang="ar">Qatar League 2024/25 - MD9</desc><category lang="ar">دوري نجوم قطر</category></programme><programme start="20241103001600" stop="20241103020400" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">Monaco vs Angers SCO - French Ligue 1 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Monaco are on a seven-game winning streak against Angers in Ligue 1, their longest ongoing run against an opponent in the top-flight. SCO have not won against ASM in L1 since September 2018 and a 1-0 win at Louis-II. Defeated 2-1 at Nice, Monaco could record consecutive defeats in Ligue 1 for the first time since the last three matchdays of the 2022/23 season, in May/June 2023.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الفرنسي</category></programme><programme start="20241103001800" stop="20241103022000" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">Girona vs Leganés - LaLiga 2024/2025 Week 12</title><desc lang="ar">Girona have not lost any of their four matches against Leganés in LaLiga, keeping a clean sheet in all of them – they are the only opponent against whom they have not conceded a single goal in the top-flight along with Málaga. At home, Girona have lost only one of their six matches in all competitions against Leganés, 0-2 in Segunda División in February 2021.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإسباني لكرة القدم</category></programme><programme start="20241103003000" stop="20241103010000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">Brighton vs Liverpool - Mini Match - Carabao Cup 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Brighton vs Liverpool - Extended Highlights - Carabao Cup 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">مباريات قصيرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103003000" stop="20241103021500" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Wolfsburg vs Augsburg - Bundesliga 2024/25 Week 9</title><desc lang="ar">VfL Wolfsburg were one of just two teams alongside 1. FC Heidenheim that FC Augsburg won both league fixtures against last season. FCA haven’t lost any of their last five Bundesliga meetings with the Wolves  – of the current top-flight sides, they’re only on a longer unbeaten run against Union Berlin. VfL Wolfsburg have won just three of their 13 Bundesliga home games against FC Augsburg. Of the sides they have faced at least three times at home in the top flight, their win percentage is only worse against FC Bayern  than it is versus FCA.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103003000" stop="20241103013000" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">Sprint Race - FIA Formula 1 World Championship -Sao Paolo GP  2024</title><desc lang="ar">beIN SPORTS is the live and exclusive broadcast partners of Formula 1 until end of 2033 season. The 2024 season has a record schedule of 24 Formula 1 races for the first time, all race weekends, including every Practice, Qualifying, Sprint &amp; Race  will be live &amp; exclusive on beIN.
</desc><category lang="ar">رياضة السيارات</category></programme><programme start="20241103003000" stop="20241103010000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Al Hassila  - 3/11/24</title><desc lang="ar">"Al Hassila" provides a concise recap of the latest sports matches, highlighting key goals and noteworthy moments from around the world of sports.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103003000" stop="20241103023000" channel="10802"><title lang="ar">Eintracht Frankfurt vs Bochum - Bundesliga 2024/25 Week 9</title><desc lang="ar">Eintracht Frankfurt are without a win in their last four meetings with VfL Bochum  – the last three clashes have ended 1-1. Of the current top-flight sides, Frankfurt have only been waiting longer for a Bundesliga win against Borussia Dortmund  than versus Bochum. Only VfL Wolfsburg  have had less possession than Eintracht Frankfurt and VfL Bochum in the Bundesliga this season. Bochum also have the worst pass accuracy in the league, as well as the fewest 10+ pass sequences.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103010000" stop="20241103013000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">NBA Action 2024/2025</title><desc lang="ar">the NBA Action round through technical readings and interviews with stars and managers of the teams



































</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103010000" stop="20241103011500" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Al Jawla  - Live Studio @02:00</title><desc lang="ar">Al Jawla covers the latest news and stories from sporting events across the planet. Including latest results and latest scores from the most recent games taking place. This daily look at the latest stories provides a fast paced update to sporting events.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103010300" stop="20241103012800" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">UEFA UCL Magazine 2024/2025 - MD3 Review</title><desc lang="ar">A recap of the best of the action, plus a look forward to the next Match Day in Europe’s premium football competition, the UEFA Champions League. This season is the first in the new format, with 36 participating teams in a league phase replacing the previous Group stage. All matches from the UEFA Champions League are live and exclusive only on beIN.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103011500" stop="20241103013000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">The summary 1 - 3/11/24</title><desc lang="ar">'"Daily Highlights" is a brief highlight of the previous days action. A look at the goals and talking points that have taken place in the world of sport. </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103012800" stop="20241103031500" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">Brest vs Nice - French Ligue 1 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Brest vs Nice was the only encounter not to have produced any goals last season in Ligue 1. Brest have 14 clean sheets against Nice in Ligue 1, at least three more than against any other opponent. In fact, SB29 could record four consecutive clean sheets against OGCN for the first time in the top-flight.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الفرنسي</category></programme><programme start="20241103013000" stop="20241103020000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">With beIN Reportes - News</title><desc lang="ar">beIN SPORTS News has more sports reporters across the planet than any other broadcaster. This program is a collection of the best of their stories from the sporting world. From the more obscure stories to the reaction to the biggest sportstaking place, the beIn reporters are constantly filing exceptional stories and this program collects the best together.  									
									
									
</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103013000" stop="20241103020000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">Leverkusen vs Stuttgart - Mini Match - Bundesliga 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Leverkusen vs Stuttgart - Extended Highlights - Bundesliga 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">مباريات قصيرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103013000" stop="20241103023000" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">DTM - Hockenheim / 2024 EP8</title><desc lang="ar">DTM. Three letters encapsulating motorsport tradition like few other racing series. Born in 1984, the DTM is coming off one of its strongest ever seasons under the guidance of the ADAC! Nine different race winners from the first nine races – including all six represented brands (Audi, BMW, Mercedes, Lamborghini, Porsche and Ferrari) – an unmistakable testament to the unique competitive balance!







</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103020000" stop="20241103023000" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">GKA Kite-Surf &amp; Hydrofoil Big Air World Cup - Sylt</title><desc lang="ar">Welcome to the northern German island of Sylt for a double-header of events on the Qatar Airways GKA Kite World Tour.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103020000" stop="20241103023000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">Lille vs Lyon - Mini Match - French Ligue 1 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Lille vs Lyon - Extended Highlights - French Ligue 1 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">مباريات قصيرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103020000" stop="20241103030000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">The Issue of The Day - 2024</title><desc lang="ar">The Issue Of The Day, from the beIn Sports News Team, takes an in depth look at the the main story form the world of sport from the last 24 hours.</desc><category lang="ar">الأخبار الرياضية</category></programme><programme start="20241103020400" stop="20241103023000" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">UEFA Nations League 2024/2025 - Best Goals MD3 &amp; MD4</title><desc lang="ar">Best goals from the third and fourth rounds of UEFA Nations League 2024/2025. </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103021500" stop="20241103024500" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Bundesliga - Special 2024/2025 Best of October</title><desc lang="ar">October started with a top of the table thriller when Eintracht Frankfurt and Bayern München played out a dramatic match. After the latest international break, the Bundesliga returned with Bayern München taking on last years runners up VfB Stuttgart as they looked to defend top spot. Eintracht Frankfurt, spearheaded by Omar Mamoush in the form of his life, looked to keep up the chases under coach Dino Toppmüller. While Marco Rose's RB Leipzig continued their early season form, as did Xavi and Lois Openda, as they stayed neck and neck with Bayern München. There was many a stunning strike as the Bundesliga continued to provide goalscoring spectacle. We relive the footballing and emotional high</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103022000" stop="20241103040500" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">River Plate (ARG) vs Atletico Mineiro (BRA) - Copa Libertadores -2024 - Semi Final  2nd Leg</title><desc lang="ar">Live and exclusive coverage only on beIN of the Copa Libertadores which is the most important international football club competition in South America. The Copa Libertadores’ rich history is saturated with many legendary matches and iconic players from the region including Pelé, Juan Carlos Lorenzo's, Zico, Riquelme, Neymar and the iconic teams such as Santos, Flamengo, Palmeiras, Boca Juniors, River Plate and São Paulo.</desc><category lang="ar">كأس ليبرتادوريس</category></programme><programme start="20241103023000" stop="20241103043000" channel="10802"><title lang="ar">Fortuna Düsseldorf  vs FC Kaiserslautern - Bundesliga 2 - 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Bundesliga 2 division is the men's second professional association football division of the German football league system. Bundesliga 2 is the ideal proving ground for younger players in Germany before stepping up to the Bundesliga, but it’s also simply a great league to watch if you want drama and excitement at a level that still boasts quality.</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني الدرجة الثانية</category></programme><programme start="20241103023000" stop="20241103041500" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">Al Sadd vs Al Rayyan - Qatar League 2024/25 - MD9</title><desc lang="ar">Qatar League 2024/25 - MD9</desc><category lang="ar">دوري نجوم قطر</category></programme><programme start="20241103023000" stop="20241103053000" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">PSG vs Lens - French Ligue 1 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Paris SG have won their last three games against Lens in Ligue 1 and could equal their best run against them in the top-flight. Paris SG have not lost any of their last eight Ligue 1 meetings with Lens, dating back to 2007/08, having lost the previous five.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الفرنسي</category></programme><programme start="20241103023000" stop="20241103030000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">The Big Interview 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">A chance to hear from one of the biggest and most interesting names in the Premier League in a more considered sit-down interview format. A thought-provoking 30-minute programme, the interviews will be detailed, topical and insightful.
























</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103023000" stop="20241103043000" channel="10801"><title lang="ar">Jannik SINNER (ITA)  vs Novak DJOKOVIC (SRB) - Fnal - ATP 1000 Rolex Shanghai Masters 2024</title><desc lang="ar">The 2024 ATP 1000 Shanghai Masters final features Jannik Sinner against Novak Djokovic. Sinner, the new world No. 1, who is chasing his seventh ATP title of the year, earned his place by defeating Tomas Machac, while Djokovic overcame Taylor Fritz despite a hip issue. Djokovic who is chasing his 100th ATP title, leads their head-to-head 4-3, but Sinner has won three of their last four meetings, including a victory at the 2024 Australian Open

</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103023000" stop="20241103033000" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">Race 1 - Formula 4 Italy Championship - Monza Round</title><desc lang="ar">The Formula 4 Italy Championship - Monza Round  is a key event in the Italian F4 series, held at the famous Monza Circuit. Known for its high speeds, Monza offers thrilling races where young drivers compete to gain valuable experience and points in their journey toward higher levels of motorsport.</desc><category lang="ar">رياضة السيارات</category></programme><programme start="20241103024500" stop="20241103043000" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Bayern München vs Union Berlin - Bundesliga 2024/25 Week 9</title><desc lang="ar">FC Bayern München haven’t lost any of their 10 Bundesliga meetings with 1. FC Union Berlin  – the only other side Bayern have faced as often in the top flight without ever losing is SV Darmstadt. Meanwhile, FCB are the only team that Union have played more than twice in the Bundesliga without ever winning. Vincent Kompany has collected 20 points in his first eight Bundesliga games as FC Bayern München head coach, the best return since Carlo Ancelotti in 2016. Only two coaches have ever had a better points haul after eight matchdays in the Bayern dugout: Otto Rehhagel in 1995  and Ottmar Hitzfeld in 1998. No coach in top-flight history has seen his side score as many goals in their first eigh</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103030000" stop="20241103054300" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">Newcastle United vs Arsenal - English Premier League 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Newcastle have won two of their last three Premier League home games against Arsenal, as many as they had in their previous 19 at St James’ Park against them combined. Arsenal lost this exact fixture 1-0 last season but haven’t lost consecutive away league games against Newcastle since their first three such visits in the Premier League between 1994 and 1996.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإنجليزي الممتاز</category></programme><programme start="20241103030000" stop="20241103040000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Al Hassad</title><desc lang="ar">Al Hassad is a nighltly studio from beIN Sports News that looks at the stories that have made the headlines in the world of sport and those stories that will be making the headlines tomorrow morning.</desc><category lang="ar">الأخبار الرياضية</category></programme><programme start="20241103031500" stop="20241103050800" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">Nottingham Forest vs West Ham United - English Premier League 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Nottingham Forest have won both of their Premier League home games against West Ham since their return to the division in 2022. They last won more consecutively against the Hammers between 1969 and 1978. West Ham have lost two of their last four Premier League games against Nottingham Forest, having lost just one of their previous 15 against them in the top-flight.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإنجليزي الممتاز</category></programme><programme start="20241103031800" stop="20241103082000" channel="10601"><title lang="ar">Argentina vs Spain- Men’s Final - Padel world championship Qatar 2024</title><desc lang="ar">Spain is set on winning back the world title from Argentina in the men’s final of the 2024 World Padel Championship.
This showdown marks their 13th meeting in the finals, where Argentina has historically led with 11 titles, compared to Spain's 4.
</desc><category lang="ar">باديل</category></programme><programme start="20241103033000" stop="20241103043000" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">Race 2 - Formula 4 Italy Championship - Monza Round</title><desc lang="ar">The Formula 4 Italy Championship - Monza Round  is a key event in the Italian F4 series, held at the famous Monza Circuit. Known for its high speeds, Monza offers thrilling races where young drivers compete to gain valuable experience and points in their journey toward higher levels of motorsport.</desc><category lang="ar">رياضة السيارات</category></programme><programme start="20241103040000" stop="20241103041500" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Al Jawla  - Live Studio @02:00</title><desc lang="ar">Al Jawla covers the latest news and stories from sporting events across the planet. Including latest results and latest scores from the most recent games taking place. This daily look at the latest stories provides a fast paced update to sporting events.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103040500" stop="20241103055000" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">Deportivo Alavés vs Mallorca - LaLiga 2024/2025 Week 12</title><desc lang="ar">Alavés have not won any of their last five matches against Mallorca in LaLiga, drawing the last two. This is the first time that these sides have drawn in two successive top-flight meetings. Mallorca have won 44.4% of their away games against Alavés in LaLiga, their highest percentage of away wins against a single opponent with at least five meetings in the top-flight.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإسباني لكرة القدم</category></programme><programme start="20241103041500" stop="20241103043000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">The summary 1 - 3/11/24</title><desc lang="ar">'"Daily Highlights" is a brief highlight of the previous days action. A look at the goals and talking points that have taken place in the world of sport. </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103041500" stop="20241103060000" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">Al Shamal vs Al Duhail - Qatar League 2024/25 - MD9</title><desc lang="ar">Qatar League 2024/25 - MD9</desc><category lang="ar">دوري نجوم قطر</category></programme><programme start="20241103043000" stop="20241103050000" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Bundesliga - Special 2024/2025 - Coaching Masterclass</title><desc lang="ar">Xabi Alonso, Vincent Kompany and Nuri Sahin. Three big personalities, with big trophy collections from their own playing days. And now all three are young coaches in charge of top Bundesliga clubs: double-winners Bayer 04 Leverkusen, record champs Bayern München and Champions League finalists Borussia Dortmund.
In our special report “Coaching Masterclass,” we take a closer look at this trio blazing a trail for a new generation of touchline tacticians. What qualities do they have in common, what sets them apart from each other, whose ideas gained traction straightaway and how do they go about the job, on and off the park? An in-depth analysis of three former world-class players now tasked wit</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103043000" stop="20241103050000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">La Liga Chronicles 2024/25 Ep.9</title><desc lang="ar">"A look back at the standout games from the most recent matchday, through extensive highlights and spectacularfootage."



































</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103043000" stop="20241103053000" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">Race 3 - Formula 4 Italy Championship - Monza Round</title><desc lang="ar">The Formula 4 Italy Championship - Monza Round  is a key event in the Italian F4 series, held at the famous Monza Circuit. Known for its high speeds, Monza offers thrilling races where young drivers compete to gain valuable experience and points in their journey toward higher levels of motorsport.</desc><category lang="ar">رياضة السيارات</category></programme><programme start="20241103043000" stop="20241103064500" channel="10801"><title lang="ar">Holger RUNE (DEN) vs Alexander ZVEREV (GER)- SF1 - ATP 1000 Rolex Paris Masters 2024</title><desc lang="ar">The Rolex Paris Masters is the ninth and final ATP Masters 1000 event of the season. As the final tournament of the regular men’s tennis season, the Palais Omnisports in Bercy showcases the cream of the crop as players vie to win the prestigious title and clinch the remaining qualifying spots in the season-ending Nitto ATP Finals.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103043000" stop="20241103080000" channel="10802"><title lang="ar">Men's Race Triathlon - PTO Las Vegas - Triathlon World Tour T100</title><desc lang="ar">The Professional Triathletes Organisation (PTO) has announced the 2024 PTO Tour will be going to Lake Las Vegas in Henderson, Nevada, with the creation of the inaugural PTO Lake Las Vegas Open on 19-20 October, 2024. Taking place around the picturesque Lake Las Vegas on the grounds of Reflection Bay Golf Club and The Westin Lake Las Vegas Resort and Spa, this will be the PTO Tour’s exciting debut in ‘the entertainment capital of the world’.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103050000" stop="20241103053000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">News Bulletin - Live Studio @03:00</title><desc lang="ar">Latest news from the beIn SPORTS News room, previewing and reviewing developments and scores with contribution from around the world from beIN's reporters.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103050000" stop="20241103064500" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Borussia Dortmund vs RB Leipzig - Bundesliga 2024/25 Week 9</title><desc lang="ar">Borussia Dortmund have lost six of their last seven competitive games against RB Leipzig, with their only win in that timeframe coming at home in the Bundesliga in 2022/23. BVB had previously gone on an eight-match unbeaten run against RBL in all competitions. This will be the 10th Bundesliga clash between Borussia Dortmund and RB Leipzig on a Saturday evening – the last three have all ended in victory for RBL, who have won five of them in total. Leipzig’s last top-flight defeat came during this primetime slot in an away match, losing 2-1 at FC Bayern in late February.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103050800" stop="20241103053800" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">The Big Interview 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">A chance to hear from one of the biggest and most interesting names in the Premier League in a more considered sit-down interview format. A thought-provoking 30-minute programme, the interviews will be detailed, topical and insightful.
























</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103053000" stop="20241103060000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Al Hassila  - 3/11/24</title><desc lang="ar">"Al Hassila" provides a concise recap of the latest sports matches, highlighting key goals and noteworthy moments from around the world of sports.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103053000" stop="20241103074500" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">Boston Celtics vs Charlotte Hornets - NBA 2024 Regular Season</title><desc lang="ar">NBA 2024 Regular Season</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الأميركي لكرة السلة</category></programme><programme start="20241103053000" stop="20241103060000" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">Lille vs Lyon - Mini Match - French Ligue 1 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Lille vs Lyon - Extended Highlights - French Ligue 1 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">مباريات قصيرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103053800" stop="20241103073400" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">Southampton vs Everton - English Premier League 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Southampton have won 13 Premier League home games against Everton – no side have they beaten more often on home soil in the competition. Though they’ve lost five of their last seven Premier League away games against Southampton, Everton won 2-1 on their last visit to St Mary’s in October 2022. They’ve not won consecutive away league games against Saints since January 1992.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإنجليزي الممتاز</category></programme><programme start="20241103054300" stop="20241103082500" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">Liverpool vs Brighton - English Premier League 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">After winning each of their first six Premier League games against Brighton, Liverpool have now won just two of their last eight. They did, however, win this exact fixture 2-1 last season. Brighton have taken five points from their last four away league games against Liverpool, more than they managed in their first 11 visits to Anfield.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإنجليزي الممتاز</category></programme><programme start="20241103055000" stop="20241103062000" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">La Liga World 2024/25 Ep.12</title><desc lang="ar"> A program of interviews and reports I  which all LALIGA clubs are represented  The program lasts 26 minutes and every week presents all the latest personal stories and the more human-interest side of the competition in a slow-paced and polished format.








































</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103060000" stop="20241103063000" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">Nikola karabatic 20 Years Of Glory</title><desc lang="ar">Renowned as one of the greatest handball players of the century, Nikola retires on May 31 after his final game with PSG Handball. His career concludes with the Paris 2024 Olympic Games. A four-time World Champion, three-time Olympic gold medalist, and three-time World Handball Player of the Year, Nikola plans to take a break from his career to spend more time with his family.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103060000" stop="20241103070000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">The Issue of The Day - 2024</title><desc lang="ar">The Issue Of The Day, from the beIn Sports News Team, takes an in depth look at the the main story form the world of sport from the last 24 hours.</desc><category lang="ar">الأخبار الرياضية</category></programme><programme start="20241103060000" stop="20241103074500" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">Brest vs Nice - French Ligue 1 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Brest vs Nice was the only encounter not to have produced any goals last season in Ligue 1. Brest have 14 clean sheets against Nice in Ligue 1, at least three more than against any other opponent. In fact, SB29 could record four consecutive clean sheets against OGCN for the first time in the top-flight.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الفرنسي</category></programme><programme start="20241103062000" stop="20241103081100" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">Osasuna vs Real Valladolid - LaLiga 2024/2025 Week 12</title><desc lang="ar">Osasuna have lost just one of their last nine matches against Real Valladolid in LaLiga although five of those ended in draws  – only against Athletic  and Valencia  have they had more draws in the top-flight than against them. At home, Osasuna have lost just one of their last 16 games against Real Valladolid in LaLiga  and have kept a clean sheet in each of their last four, their longest run without conceding at home to the Castilians in the top-flight.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإسباني لكرة القدم</category></programme><programme start="20241103063000" stop="20241103080000" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">Nimes  vs Aix - LNH Division 1 - French Handball Starligue</title><desc lang="ar">Dive into the excitement of French handball with Liqui Moly Starligue, formerly LNH Division 1. Established in 1952, this premier league event features 16 top teams battling for glory. With Montpellier’s  14 Handball titles and Paris Saint-Germain's 11 wins, the competition is fierce. Champions earn spots in the EHF Champions League, while cup winners qualify for the European League.</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الفرنسي لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103064500" stop="20241103100000" channel="10801"><title lang="ar">Karen KHACHANOV vs Ugo HUMBERT (FRA)- SF2 - ATP 1000 Rolex Paris Masters 2024</title><desc lang="ar">The Rolex Paris Masters is the ninth and final ATP Masters 1000 event of the season. As the final tournament of the regular men’s tennis season, the Palais Omnisports in Bercy showcases the cream of the crop as players vie to win the prestigious title and clinch the remaining qualifying spots in the season-ending Nitto ATP Finals.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103064500" stop="20241103083000" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Eintracht Frankfurt vs Bochum - Bundesliga 2024/25 Week 9</title><desc lang="ar">Eintracht Frankfurt are without a win in their last four meetings with VfL Bochum  – the last three clashes have ended 1-1. Of the current top-flight sides, Frankfurt have only been waiting longer for a Bundesliga win against Borussia Dortmund  than versus Bochum. Only VfL Wolfsburg  have had less possession than Eintracht Frankfurt and VfL Bochum in the Bundesliga this season. Bochum also have the worst pass accuracy in the league, as well as the fewest 10+ pass sequences.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103070000" stop="20241103080000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Al Hassad</title><desc lang="ar">Al Hassad is a nighltly studio from beIN Sports News that looks at the stories that have made the headlines in the world of sport and those stories that will be making the headlines tomorrow morning.</desc><category lang="ar">الأخبار الرياضية</category></programme><programme start="20241103073400" stop="20241103092600" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">Ipswich Town vs Leicester City -English Premier League 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Ipswich have won all three of their Premier League home games against Leicester – 4-1 in January 1995, 2-0 in January 2001 and 2-0 in December 2001. Leicester have lost just one of their last nine league games against Ipswich, with both meetings between the sides in the Championship last season finishing level.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإنجليزي الممتاز</category></programme><programme start="20241103074500" stop="20241103093000" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">Saint-Étienne vs Strasbourg - French Ligue 1 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">St Etienne will host Strasbourg in Ligue 1 for the first time since February 20, 2022, when they drew 2-2. ASSE are unbeaten in their last five home games against RSCA in the top-flight. St Etienne have fewer than 10 points after nine games in a Ligue 1 season for the second consecutive time, a situation that had never occurred in their previous 16 seasons in the top-flight.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الفرنسي</category></programme><programme start="20241103074500" stop="20241103084500" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">Sprint Race - FIA Formula 1 World Championship -Sao Paolo GP  2024</title><desc lang="ar">beIN SPORTS is the live and exclusive broadcast partners of Formula 1 until end of 2033 season. The 2024 season has a record schedule of 24 Formula 1 races for the first time, all race weekends, including every Practice, Qualifying, Sprint &amp; Race  will be live &amp; exclusive on beIN.
</desc><category lang="ar">رياضة السيارات</category></programme><programme start="20241103080000" stop="20241103081500" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Al Jawla  - Live Studio @02:00</title><desc lang="ar">Al Jawla covers the latest news and stories from sporting events across the planet. Including latest results and latest scores from the most recent games taking place. This daily look at the latest stories provides a fast paced update to sporting events.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103080000" stop="20241103093000" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">Toulouse  vs St Raphael - LNH Division 1 - French Handball Starligue</title><desc lang="ar">Dive into the excitement of French handball with Liqui Moly Starligue, formerly LNH Division 1. Established in 1952, this premier league event features 16 top teams battling for glory. With Montpellier’s  14 Handball titles and Paris Saint-Germain's 11 wins, the competition is fierce. Champions earn spots in the EHF Champions League, while cup winners qualify for the European League.</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الفرنسي لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103080000" stop="20241103103000" channel="10802"><title lang="ar">Triathlon SuperTri  -Triathlon  Toulouse France 2024</title><desc lang="ar">The 2024 SuperTri Triathlon in Toulouse, France, brings together elite athletes for a fast-paced and thrilling competition. Athletes will push their limits across swimming, cycling, and running events on a scenic course through the heart of Toulouse. With top international triathletes participating, the event promises exciting performances and intense rivalries as they compete for victory in one of the sport's most prestigious events.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103081100" stop="20241103100000" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">Girona vs Leganés - LaLiga 2024/2025 Week 12</title><desc lang="ar">Girona have not lost any of their four matches against Leganés in LaLiga, keeping a clean sheet in all of them – they are the only opponent against whom they have not conceded a single goal in the top-flight along with Málaga. At home, Girona have lost only one of their six matches in all competitions against Leganés, 0-2 in Segunda División in February 2021.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإسباني لكرة القدم</category></programme><programme start="20241103081500" stop="20241103083000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Where Are They ?</title><desc lang="ar">'Where Are They?" is a special feature on a personality from a previous era of sporting achievement. The report traces where they have been and where they now are after their time as one of the leading sports men or women of their generation. </desc><category lang="ar">الأخبار الرياضية</category></programme><programme start="20241103082000" stop="20241103102000" channel="10601"><title lang="ar">Jessica CASTELLO LOPEZ ESP Alejandra SALAZAR BENGOECHEA ESP vs Marta ORTEGA GALLEGO ESP Sofia ARAUJO</title><desc lang="ar">The 2024 NewGiza Premier Padel P2 takes place from October 21-27 at the NewGiza Sports Club in Egypt. With a €250,000 prize pool, it features top international male and female players competing for ranking points and glory in one of the region’s premier padel events</desc><category lang="ar">باديل</category></programme><programme start="20241103082500" stop="20241103110000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">Wolverhampton Wanderers vs Crystal Palace - English Premier League 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">All six Premier League games between Wolves and Crystal Palace at Molineux have been won by a two-goal margin – Wolves’ three wins have all be 2-0, while the Eagles have won 2-0 twice and 3-1 once. Crystal Palace have won six of their last seven Premier League games against Wolves, as many wins as they’d managed in their previous 20 league matches against them.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإنجليزي الممتاز</category></programme><programme start="20241103083000" stop="20241103090000" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Bundesliga - Special 2024/2025 Strikers</title><desc lang="ar">Strikers: Kane, Boniface &amp; Guirassy - the Bundesliga's best
Harry Kane of Bayern München, Bayer 04 Leverkusen’s Victor Boniface and Borussia Dortmund summer signing Serhou Guirassy. Three of the Bundesliga’s deadliest scorers, each with his own distinct style, in the spotlight in our upcoming special report “Strikers: Kane, Boniface &amp; Guirassy - the Bundesliga's best”.
Forward legend Jürgen Klinsmann gives us his expert take on the trio: the qualities that make them so dangerous, their particular individual strengths and respective styles of play.  </desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103083000" stop="20241103090000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">With beIN Reportes - News</title><desc lang="ar">beIN SPORTS News has more sports reporters across the planet than any other broadcaster. This program is a collection of the best of their stories from the sporting world. From the more obscure stories to the reaction to the biggest sportstaking place, the beIn reporters are constantly filing exceptional stories and this program collects the best together.  									
									
									
</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103084500" stop="20241103094500" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">DTM - Hockenheim / 2024 EP8</title><desc lang="ar">DTM. Three letters encapsulating motorsport tradition like few other racing series. Born in 1984, the DTM is coming off one of its strongest ever seasons under the guidance of the ADAC! Nine different race winners from the first nine races – including all six represented brands (Audi, BMW, Mercedes, Lamborghini, Porsche and Ferrari) – an unmistakable testament to the unique competitive balance!







</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103090000" stop="20241103100000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">The Issue of The Day - 2024</title><desc lang="ar">The Issue Of The Day, from the beIn Sports News Team, takes an in depth look at the the main story form the world of sport from the last 24 hours.</desc><category lang="ar">الأخبار الرياضية</category></programme><programme start="20241103090000" stop="20241103104500" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Holstein Kiel vs Heidenheim - Bundesliga 2024/25 Week 9</title><desc lang="ar">Holstein Kiel are the 58th Bundesliga debutants, while 1. FC Heidenheim became the 57th last season. The Storks have lost just one their last six competitive home games against FCH, a 1-0 defeat in February 2020. The last meeting between the sides in Kiel in October 2022 finished in a 3-1 win for the hosts. With just two points from their first eight games, Holstein Kiel have made the worst start of any Bundesliga newcomer. The Storks are also the first team to concede at least two goals in each of the first eight matches in their top-flight history.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103092600" stop="20241103095000" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">UEFA UCL Magazine 2024/2025 - MD3 Review</title><desc lang="ar">A recap of the best of the action, plus a look forward to the next Match Day in Europe’s premium football competition, the UEFA Champions League. This season is the first in the new format, with 36 participating teams in a league phase replacing the previous Group stage. All matches from the UEFA Champions League are live and exclusive only on beIN.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103093000" stop="20241103103000" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">Kaiser - Handball Documentary</title><desc lang="ar">During the euro of handball 2024 In Germany, French handball team have won one of the greatest title in the history.  In this documentary we discover the sensation of the champions behind the scene how they reach the stage of the final after difficult games and catch the cup against Denmark in a dramatic final 
Kaiser is another story of success 
</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103093000" stop="20241103095900" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">UEFA Nations League 2024/2025 - Best Goals MD3 &amp; MD4</title><desc lang="ar">Best goals from the third and fourth rounds of UEFA Nations League 2024/2025. </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103094500" stop="20241103104500" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">Sprint Race Qualifying - FIA Formula 1 World Championship -Sao Paolo GP  2024</title><desc lang="ar">beIN SPORTS is the live and exclusive broadcast partners of Formula 1 until end of 2033 season. The 2024 season has a record schedule of 24 Formula 1 races for the first time, all race weekends, including every Practice, Qualifying, Sprint &amp; Race  will be live &amp; exclusive on beIN.
</desc><category lang="ar">رياضة السيارات</category></programme><programme start="20241103095000" stop="20241103113500" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">AFC Bournemouth vs Manchester City - English Premier League 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Bournemouth have won none of their 20 league games against Man City. It’s the most one side has faced another without ever winning in English Football League history. Manchester City have won all 14 of their Premier League games against Bournemouth by an aggregate score of 45-7. It’s the best 100% record any team has against another in English top-flight history.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإنجليزي الممتاز</category></programme><programme start="20241103095900" stop="20241103114500" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">Lille vs Olympique Lyonnais - French Ligue 1 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Lille lost their last game against Lyon in Ligue 1  but have not recorded two consecutive defeats against OL in the top-flight since the 2006-07 season. Lille have won only one of their last eight Ligue 1 games against Lyon, winning 1-0 in March 2020.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الفرنسي</category></programme><programme start="20241103100000" stop="20241103103000" channel="10801"><title lang="ar">Jannik Sinner vs Taylor Fritz - Men's Singles Final - Mini Matches - US Open 2024</title><desc lang="ar">Extended highlights of key matches from the US Open 2024 </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103100000" stop="20241103101500" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Al Jawla  - Live Studio @02:00</title><desc lang="ar">Al Jawla covers the latest news and stories from sporting events across the planet. Including latest results and latest scores from the most recent games taking place. This daily look at the latest stories provides a fast paced update to sporting events.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103100000" stop="20241103102600" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">LaLiga Power Ep.1</title><desc lang="ar">LALIGA Power is a program that pays tribute to all those who inspire the world through the values of football. In each episode, we discover the passion celebrities have for their club and experience a match day with the most dedicated fans in the world, as well as showing curiosities about LALIGA clubs and players. Because they are the strength of our football.








</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103101500" stop="20241103103000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">The summary 1 - 3/11/24</title><desc lang="ar">'"Daily Highlights" is a brief highlight of the previous days action. A look at the goals and talking points that have taken place in the world of sport. </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103102000" stop="20241103125000" channel="10601"><title lang="ar">Franco STUPACZUK ARG Miguel YANGUAS ESP vs Javier GARRIDO ESP Lucas BERGAMINI BRA - Final Men - Prem</title><desc lang="ar">The 2024 NewGiza Premier Padel P2 takes place from October 21-27 at the NewGiza Sports Club in Egypt. With a €250,000 prize pool, it features top international male and female players competing for ranking points and glory in one of the region’s premier padel events</desc><category lang="ar">باديل</category></programme><programme start="20241103102600" stop="20241103121500" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">Peñarol (URU) vs Botafogo (BRA) - Copa Libertadores -2024 - Semi Final  2nd Leg</title><desc lang="ar">Live and exclusive coverage only on beIN of the Copa Libertadores which is the most important international football club competition in South America. The Copa Libertadores’ rich history is saturated with many legendary matches and iconic players from the region including Pelé, Juan Carlos Lorenzo's, Zico, Riquelme, Neymar and the iconic teams such as Santos, Flamengo, Palmeiras, Boca Juniors, River Plate and São Paulo.</desc><category lang="ar">كأس ليبرتادوريس</category></programme><programme start="20241103103000" stop="20241103104500" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Special Interview  - 3/11/24</title><desc lang="ar">A  daily Special Interview related to an important issue of the day. The interview offers the background and insight into the issue chosen from the world of sport. </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103103000" stop="20241103124500" channel="10801"><title lang="ar">Holger RUNE (DEN) vs Alexander ZVEREV (GER)- SF1 - ATP 1000 Rolex Paris Masters 2024</title><desc lang="ar">The Rolex Paris Masters is the ninth and final ATP Masters 1000 event of the season. As the final tournament of the regular men’s tennis season, the Palais Omnisports in Bercy showcases the cream of the crop as players vie to win the prestigious title and clinch the remaining qualifying spots in the season-ending Nitto ATP Finals.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103103000" stop="20241103110000" channel="10802"><title lang="ar">Athletics in Olympic games - Paris 2024 - HL - Short Course</title><desc lang="ar">Summary of the men's and women's - short distance race finals . at Athletics Olympic games – Paris 2024 </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103103000" stop="20241103123000" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">USA vs Korea DPR - FIFA U17 Women's World Cup Dominican Rep. 2024 - Semi Final</title><desc lang="ar">FIFA U17 Women's World Cup Dominican Rep. 2024 - Semi Final</desc><category lang="ar">كأس العالم تحت 17 سنة</category></programme><programme start="20241103104500" stop="20241103123000" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Hoffenheim vs St. Pauli - Bundesliga 2024/25 Week 9</title><desc lang="ar">Both of TSG Hoffenheim’s home games against FC St. Pauli have ended in draws: 1-1 in the second division in 2007/08 and 2-2 in the Bundesliga in 2010/11. The two sides teams have each won in Hamburg, meaning their head-to-head record is even after four competitive meetings. TSG are still unbeaten against St. Pauli in the top flight. TSG Hoffenheim have won just one of their last seven Bundesliga matches, a 3-1 victory over Bochum in their last home game. Hoffenheim’s current tally of eight points after eight matchdays has only been worse in the top flight in 2015/16. However, TSG are unbeaten in three games  after previously suffering four straight defeats.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103104500" stop="20241103111500" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">GP Confidential 2024 / Magazine</title><desc lang="ar">Explore the sporting secrets of F1. Across 25 episodes and in crisp 3D animations, we analyses the technical details, which decide which teams make the most of the rules - and which need to go back to the drawing board. Complemented by features on historical milestones as well as race previews - GP Confidential is the perfect treat for any F1 fan.
























</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103104500" stop="20241103110000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Special Report - 3/11/24</title><desc lang="ar">"Special Report" is a single long feature from one of beIN SPORTS News reporters that takes an alternative look at a subject from the world of sport. </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103110000" stop="20241103134500" channel="10802"><title lang="ar">SuperTri Triathlon - NEOM</title><desc lang="ar" /><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103110000" stop="20241103113000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">EPL Stories  2024/2025</title><desc lang="ar">Showcases the personalities who have shaped the Premier League era with a focus on the stories that resonate with international audiences.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103110000" stop="20241103113000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">News Bulletin - Live Studio @03:00</title><desc lang="ar">Latest news from the beIn SPORTS News room, previewing and reviewing developments and scores with contribution from around the world from beIN's reporters.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103111500" stop="20241103114500" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">Fast Zone / 2024</title><desc lang="ar">Covering everything from prototypes to endurance racing, karting to airplanes and even some real oddities… With both tradition and a fresh take on motorsport, Fast/Zone is the ultimate resource for everything that is fast and fascinating!







































</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103113000" stop="20241103120000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Al Hassila  - 3/11/24</title><desc lang="ar">"Al Hassila" provides a concise recap of the latest sports matches, highlighting key goals and noteworthy moments from around the world of sports.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103113000" stop="20241103120000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">Newcastle vs Arsenal - Mini Match - English Premier League 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Newcastle vs Arsenal - Extended Highlights - English Premier League 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">مباريات قصيرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103113500" stop="20241103133000" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">Nottingham Forest vs West Ham United - English Premier League 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Nottingham Forest have won both of their Premier League home games against West Ham since their return to the division in 2022. They last won more consecutively against the Hammers between 1969 and 1978. West Ham have lost two of their last four Premier League games against Nottingham Forest, having lost just one of their previous 15 against them in the top-flight.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإنجليزي الممتاز</category></programme><programme start="20241103114500" stop="20241103132800" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">PSG vs Lens - French Ligue 1 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Paris SG have won their last three games against Lens in Ligue 1 and could equal their best run against them in the top-flight. Paris SG have not lost any of their last eight Ligue 1 meetings with Lens, dating back to 2007/08, having lost the previous five.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الفرنسي</category></programme><programme start="20241103114500" stop="20241103124500" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">Gran Premio D’italia Race Review Show - FIA Formula 1 World Championship</title><desc lang="ar">Best Moments of the beIN Coverage and the Race of GRAN PREMIO D’ITALIA 2024
</desc><category lang="ar">حصيلة الدوريات</category></programme><programme start="20241103120000" stop="20241103130000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Three O'Clock bulletin - NEWS</title><desc lang="ar">Latest news from the beIn SPORTS News room, previewing and reviewing developments and scores with contribution from around the world from beIN's reporters.</desc><category lang="ar">الأخبار الرياضية</category></programme><programme start="20241103120000" stop="20241103123000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">Bournemouth vs Man City - Mini Match - English Premier League 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Bournemouth vs Man City - Extended Highlights - English Premier League 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">مباريات قصيرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103121500" stop="20241103140000" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">Deportivo Alavés vs Mallorca - LaLiga 2024/2025 Week 12</title><desc lang="ar">Alavés have not won any of their last five matches against Mallorca in LaLiga, drawing the last two. This is the first time that these sides have drawn in two successive top-flight meetings. Mallorca have won 44.4% of their away games against Alavés in LaLiga, their highest percentage of away wins against a single opponent with at least five meetings in the top-flight.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإسباني لكرة القدم</category></programme><programme start="20241103123000" stop="20241103130000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">Liverpool vs Brighton - Mini Match - English Premier League 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Liverpool vs Brighton - Extended Highlights - English Premier League 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">مباريات قصيرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103123000" stop="20241103130000" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Leverkusen vs Stuttgart - Mini Match - Bundesliga 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Leverkusen vs Stuttgart - Extended Highlights - Bundesliga 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">مباريات قصيرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103123000" stop="20241103143000" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">Spain vs England - FIFA U17 Women's World Cup Dominican Rep. 2024 - Semi Final</title><desc lang="ar">FIFA U17 Women's World Cup Dominican Rep. 2024 - Semi Final</desc><category lang="ar">كأس العالم تحت 17 سنة</category></programme><programme start="20241103124500" stop="20241103134500" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">Sprint Race - FIA Formula 1 World Championship -Sao Paolo GP  2024</title><desc lang="ar">beIN SPORTS is the live and exclusive broadcast partners of Formula 1 until end of 2033 season. The 2024 season has a record schedule of 24 Formula 1 races for the first time, all race weekends, including every Practice, Qualifying, Sprint &amp; Race  will be live &amp; exclusive on beIN.
</desc><category lang="ar">رياضة السيارات</category></programme><programme start="20241103124500" stop="20241103140000" channel="10801"><title lang="ar">BIG ITW Victoria Azarenka</title><desc lang="ar">Former World Number One Victoria Azarenka looks back on the key moments of her life and career including her two Grand Slam victories.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103125000" stop="20241103150500" channel="10601"><title lang="ar">Atlético Madrid vs Las Palmas - LaLiga 2024/2025 Week 12</title><desc lang="ar">Atletico Madrid have won nine of their last 10 matches against Las Palmas in LaLiga, keeping a clean sheet in eight of those games and scoring at least three goals in six of them. At home, Atlético de Madrid have not lost any of their last 20 matches against Las Palmas in LaLiga, winning the last five without conceding a goal; their longest run of clean sheets against the Canaries at home in the top-flight.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإسباني لكرة القدم</category></programme><programme start="20241103130000" stop="20241103133000" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Bayern Munich vs Union Berlin - Mini Match - Bundesliga 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Bayern Munich vs Union Berlin - Extended Highlights - Bundesliga 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">مباريات قصيرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103130000" stop="20241103131500" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Al Jawla  - Live Studio @16:00</title><desc lang="ar">Al Jawla covers the latest news and stories from sporting events across the planet. Including latest results and latest scores from the most recent games taking place. This daily look at the latest stories provides a fast paced update to sporting events.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103130000" stop="20241103133000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">Girona vs Leganes - Mini Match - La Liga 2024/2025</title><desc lang="ar">Girona vs Leganes - Extended Highlights - La Liga 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإسباني لكرة القدم</category></programme><programme start="20241103131500" stop="20241103133000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Stats - 3/11/24</title><desc lang="ar">An in depth look at the statistics that have emerged from the latest sporting events. All the data and facts for an even deeper understanding of the sporting world </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103132800" stop="20241103135000" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">Ligue 1: Iconic Players Best of Blanc , Ibrahimovic and Niang in Ligue 1</title><desc lang="ar">Ligue 1 Legends, program talks about the main achievements and numbers of three legends played in French league. Laurent Blanc , Zlatan Ibrahimovic and Mamadou Niang.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103133000" stop="20241103140000" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Dortmund vs Leipzig - Mini Match - Bundesliga 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Dortmund vs Leipzig - Extended Highlights - Bundesliga 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">مباريات قصيرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103133000" stop="20241103162800" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">Tottenham vs Aston Villa - English Premier League 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Tottenham have lost three of their last four Premier League meetings with Aston Villa, though did win the last such match 4-0 in March. They’d only lost two of their previous 21 against the Villans. Aston Villa have won three of their last four Premier League away games against Tottenham, including the last two in a row under Unai Emery. They last won three consecutive away league games against Spurs between 1922 and 1924.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإنجليزي الممتاز</category></programme><programme start="20241103133000" stop="20241103135800" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">EPL Stories  2024/2025</title><desc lang="ar">Showcases the personalities who have shaped the Premier League era with a focus on the stories that resonate with international audiences.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103133000" stop="20241103134500" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Special Interview  - 3/11/24</title><desc lang="ar">A  daily Special Interview related to an important issue of the day. The interview offers the background and insight into the issue chosen from the world of sport. </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103134500" stop="20241103140000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">The summary 1 - 3/11/24</title><desc lang="ar">'"Daily Highlights" is a brief highlight of the previous days action. A look at the goals and talking points that have taken place in the world of sport. </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103134500" stop="20241103144500" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">DTM - Hockenheim / 2024 EP8</title><desc lang="ar">DTM. Three letters encapsulating motorsport tradition like few other racing series. Born in 1984, the DTM is coming off one of its strongest ever seasons under the guidance of the ADAC! Nine different race winners from the first nine races – including all six represented brands (Audi, BMW, Mercedes, Lamborghini, Porsche and Ferrari) – an unmistakable testament to the unique competitive balance!







</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103134500" stop="20241103154500" channel="10802"><title lang="ar">Paris vs Toulouse - Marmara Spike ligue Volleyball 2024</title><desc lang="ar">The LNV Ligue A Masculine (LAM), currently known as the Marmara SpikeLigue for sponsorship reasons, is the top-tier men's volleyball league in France, established in 1938. Governed by the Ligue Nationale de Volley (LNV) under the French Volleyball Federation (FFVB), the league features France's elite volleyball talent. Formerly called Pro A until 2009, it shares a rich history and prestige akin to its basketball counterpart.

</desc><category lang="ar">الكرة الطائرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103135000" stop="20241103160000" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">Toulouse vs Reims - French Ligue 1 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">This will be the 50th meeting between Toulouse and Reims in Ligue 1. TFC have won only two of their last six matches against SDR in Ligue 1, after winning five of the previous seven. Toulouse have only lost one home game against Reims in Ligue 1 in the last 60 years, losing in December 2019.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الفرنسي</category></programme><programme start="20241103135800" stop="20241103142500" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">Liverpool vs Brighton - Mini Match - English Premier League 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Liverpool vs Brighton - Extended Highlights - English Premier League 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">مباريات قصيرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103140000" stop="20241103143000" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">Girona vs Leganes - Mini Match - La Liga 2024/2025</title><desc lang="ar">Girona vs Leganes - Extended Highlights - La Liga 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإسباني لكرة القدم</category></programme><programme start="20241103140000" stop="20241103143000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">News Bulletin - @17:00</title><desc lang="ar">Latest news from the beIn SPORTS News room, previewing and reviewing developments and scores with contribution from around the world from beIN's reporters.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103140000" stop="20241103160000" channel="10801"><title lang="ar">Final ATP 1000 Rolex Paris Masters 2024</title><desc lang="ar">The Rolex Paris Masters is the ninth and final ATP Masters 1000 event of the season. As the final tournament of the regular men’s tennis season, the Palais Omnisports in Bercy showcases the cream of the crop as players vie to win the prestigious title and clinch the remaining qualifying spots in the season-ending Nitto ATP Finals.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103140000" stop="20241103142000" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Europa League 2024/2025 - Best Goals of MD3</title><desc lang="ar">The best goals from third round of Europa League.

</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الأوروبي</category></programme><programme start="20241103142000" stop="20241103163000" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Freiburg vs Mainz 05 - Bundesliga 2024/25 Week 9</title><desc lang="ar">SC Freiburg and 1. FSV Mainz 05 are set to meet for the 49th time across all competitions and the 31st time in the Bundesliga. SC are currently unbeaten in each of the last six Bundesliga clashes between the sides, the longest unbeaten run for either team in this match-up in the top flight. SC Freiburg have won three of their four Bundesliga home games under head coach Julian Schuster, more than they managed across their last 13 games on home soil under Christian Streich combined.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103142500" stop="20241103145500" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">Bournemouth vs Man City - Mini Match - English Premier League 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Bournemouth vs Man City - Extended Highlights - English Premier League 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">مباريات قصيرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103143000" stop="20241103150000" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">Nikola karabatic 20 Years Of Glory</title><desc lang="ar">Renowned as one of the greatest handball players of the century, Nikola retires on May 31 after his final game with PSG Handball. His career concludes with the Paris 2024 Olympic Games. A four-time World Champion, three-time Olympic gold medalist, and three-time World Handball Player of the Year, Nikola plans to take a break from his career to spend more time with his family.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103143000" stop="20241103174500" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">Barcelona vs Espanyol - LaLiga 2024/2025 Week 12</title><desc lang="ar">Espanyol have now gone 26 straight derbies without a win against Barcelona in LaLiga ; the worst winless run against an opponent in their top-flight history, and the worst winless run of any team in any regional derby in the competition. Barcelona have not lost any of their last 13 home games against Espanyol in LaLiga, since a 1-2 defeat in February 2009 with Josep Guardiola as Blaugrana coach and Mauricio Pochettino on the Espanyol bench.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإسباني لكرة القدم</category></programme><programme start="20241103143000" stop="20241103150000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Bundesliga - Special 2024/2025 Best of October</title><desc lang="ar">October started with a top of the table thriller when Eintracht Frankfurt and Bayern München played out a dramatic match. After the latest international break, the Bundesliga returned with Bayern München taking on last years runners up VfB Stuttgart as they looked to defend top spot. Eintracht Frankfurt, spearheaded by Omar Mamoush in the form of his life, looked to keep up the chases under coach Dino Toppmüller. While Marco Rose's RB Leipzig continued their early season form, as did Xavi and Lois Openda, as they stayed neck and neck with Bayern München. There was many a stunning strike as the Bundesliga continued to provide goalscoring spectacle. We relive the footballing and emotional high</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103144500" stop="20241103153000" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">F1 Mexico Grand Prix Highlights</title><desc lang="ar">F1 Mexico Grand Prix - Extended Highlights </desc><category lang="ar">بطولة العالم للدراجات النارية</category></programme><programme start="20241103145500" stop="20241103165800" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">Millwall vs Burnley - EFL - English Football League  - Championship 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">EFL - English Football League  - Championship 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">دوري البطولة الإنجليزية - الدرجة الأولى</category></programme><programme start="20241103150000" stop="20241103164500" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">PSG  vs Montpellier - LNH Division 1 - French Handball Starligue</title><desc lang="ar">Dive into the excitement of French handball with Liqui Moly Starligue, formerly LNH Division 1. Established in 1952, this premier league event features 16 top teams battling for glory. With Montpellier’s  14 Handball titles and Paris Saint-Germain's 11 wins, the competition is fierce. Champions earn spots in the EHF Champions League, while cup winners qualify for the European League.</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الفرنسي لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103150000" stop="20241103160000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">News Bulletin - @18:00</title><desc lang="ar">Latest news from the beIn SPORTS News room, previewing and reviewing developments and scores with contribution from around the world from beIN's reporters.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103150500" stop="20241103172000" channel="10601"><title lang="ar">Almeria vs Cordoba - LaLiga Hypermotion 2024-2025  - Spanish La liga 2</title><desc lang="ar">LaLiga Hypermotion 2024-2025  contested by 22 teams, with the top two teams plus the winner of a play-off promoted to La Liga and replaced by the three lowest-placed teams in that division.</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الأسباني للدرجة الثانية</category></programme><programme start="20241103153000" stop="20241103193000" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">Main Race - FIA Formula 1 World Championship -Sao Paolo GP  2024</title><desc lang="ar">beIN SPORTS is the live and exclusive broadcast partners of Formula 1 until end of 2033 season. The 2024 season has a record schedule of 24 Formula 1 races for the first time, all race weekends, including every Practice, Qualifying, Sprint &amp; Race  will be live &amp; exclusive on beIN.
</desc><category lang="ar">رياضة السيارات</category></programme><programme start="20241103154500" stop="20241103170000" channel="10802"><title lang="ar">Road To Gold Medal – Imen Khelif - Algeria - Paris 2024</title><desc lang="ar">follows the inspiring journey of Algerian boxer Imane Khelif as she competes in the 66 kg weight category at the 2024 Paris Olympic Games. After a controversial setback in a previous competition, Khelif is determined to come back stronger and claim the gold medal. This feature highlights her resilience, key fights, and unwavering dedication as she fights to bring glory to Algeria on the world stage.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103160000" stop="20241103162000" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">Do You Know "Legend" Franz Beckenbauer</title><desc lang="ar">The most amazing and unknown stories about Frantz Beckenbauer</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103160000" stop="20241103161500" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Al Jawla  - Live Studio @19:00</title><desc lang="ar">Al Jawla covers the latest news and stories from sporting events across the planet. Including latest results and latest scores from the most recent games taking place. This daily look at the latest stories provides a fast paced update to sporting events.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103160000" stop="20241103183000" channel="10801"><title lang="ar">Jack DRAPER (GBR) vs Karen KHACHANOV - Final Erste Bank Open 2024 - ATP 500</title><desc lang="ar">Jack Draper takes on Karen Khachanov in an exciting showdown. Draper has been in stellar form, advancing smoothly, while Khachanov enters on an impressive eight-match winning streak after his Almaty title. The two recently faced off in close matches, with Khachanov holding the head-to-head edge. This final promises a compelling clash of Draper’s resilience against Khachanov’s experience.


</desc><category lang="ar">تنس</category></programme><programme start="20241103161500" stop="20241103163000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Stats - 3/11/24</title><desc lang="ar">An in depth look at the statistics that have emerged from the latest sporting events. All the data and facts for an even deeper understanding of the sporting world </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103162000" stop="20241103183000" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">Borussia Mönchengladbach vs Werder Bremen - Bundesliga 2024/25 Week 9</title><desc lang="ar">SV Werder Bremen have won just one of their last 15 Bundesliga games against Borussia Mönchengladbach. However, Werder haven’t lost any of their four Bundesliga games against the Foals since being promoted back to the top flight  — it’s their longest unbeaten run against Gladbach in the division since going five games without defeat from October 1997 to September 2001. Borussia Mönchengladbach have more Bundesliga home wins against SV Werder Bremen than against any other side. Since a 4-1 defeat in October 2010, the Foals are unbeaten in each of their last 12 top-flight home matches against SVW  — it’s their longest run against any side currently playing in the division.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103162800" stop="20241103193000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">Manchester United vs Chelsea - English Premier League 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Manchester United are unbeaten in their last 11 home league games against Chelsea, and are looking to win three in a row against the Blues at Old Trafford for the first time since January 1957. Despite trailing in stoppage time, Chelsea won their last Premier League game against Man Utd 4-3 in April. They last won consecutive league meetings with the Red Devils in March 2011.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإنجليزي الممتاز</category></programme><programme start="20241103163000" stop="20241103170000" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Bundesliga - Special 2024/2025 - Coaching Masterclass</title><desc lang="ar">Xabi Alonso, Vincent Kompany and Nuri Sahin. Three big personalities, with big trophy collections from their own playing days. And now all three are young coaches in charge of top Bundesliga clubs: double-winners Bayer 04 Leverkusen, record champs Bayern München and Champions League finalists Borussia Dortmund.
In our special report “Coaching Masterclass,” we take a closer look at this trio blazing a trail for a new generation of touchline tacticians. What qualities do they have in common, what sets them apart from each other, whose ideas gained traction straightaway and how do they go about the job, on and off the park? An in-depth analysis of three former world-class players now tasked wit</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103163000" stop="20241103164500" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Special Interview  - 3/11/24</title><desc lang="ar">A  daily Special Interview related to an important issue of the day. The interview offers the background and insight into the issue chosen from the world of sport. </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103164500" stop="20241103170000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Special Report - 3/11/24</title><desc lang="ar">"Special Report" is a single long feature from one of beIN SPORTS News reporters that takes an alternative look at a subject from the world of sport. </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103164500" stop="20241103174500" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">Kaiser - Handball Documentary</title><desc lang="ar">During the euro of handball 2024 In Germany, French handball team have won one of the greatest title in the history.  In this documentary we discover the sensation of the champions behind the scene how they reach the stage of the final after difficult games and catch the cup against Denmark in a dramatic final 
Kaiser is another story of success 
</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103165800" stop="20241103172600" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">The Big Interview 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">A chance to hear from one of the biggest and most interesting names in the Premier League in a more considered sit-down interview format. A thought-provoking 30-minute programme, the interviews will be detailed, topical and insightful.
























</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103170000" stop="20241103190000" channel="10802"><title lang="ar">Pit Lane Main Race - FIA Formula 1 World Championship -Sao Paolo GP  2024</title><desc lang="ar">beIN SPORTS is the live and exclusive broadcast partners of Formula 1 until end of 2033 season. The 2024 season has a record schedule of 24 Formula 1 races for the first time, all race weekends, including every Practice, Qualifying, Sprint &amp; Race  will be live &amp; exclusive on beIN.
</desc><category lang="ar">رياضة السيارات</category></programme><programme start="20241103170000" stop="20241103173000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Sign Language Bulletin @20:00</title><desc lang="ar">A special News Bulletin from the beIN SPORTS News Room with the addition of sign language for the hard of hearing.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103170000" stop="20241103184500" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Bayern München vs Union Berlin - Bundesliga 2024/25 Week 9</title><desc lang="ar">FC Bayern München haven’t lost any of their 10 Bundesliga meetings with 1. FC Union Berlin  – the only other side Bayern have faced as often in the top flight without ever losing is SV Darmstadt. Meanwhile, FCB are the only team that Union have played more than twice in the Bundesliga without ever winning. Vincent Kompany has collected 20 points in his first eight Bundesliga games as FC Bayern München head coach, the best return since Carlo Ancelotti in 2016. Only two coaches have ever had a better points haul after eight matchdays in the Bayern dugout: Otto Rehhagel in 1995  and Ottmar Hitzfeld in 1998. No coach in top-flight history has seen his side score as many goals in their first eigh</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103172000" stop="20241103193000" channel="10601"><title lang="ar">Sevilla vs Real Sociedad - LaLiga 2024/2025 Week 12</title><desc lang="ar">Sevilla won their last meeting with Real Sociedad in LaLiga, 3-2 in March 2024, having failed to win any of their previous five. However, they have conceded exactly two goals in each of their last four meetings with the San Sebastian side in the competition. Sevilla have lost just one of their last eight LaLiga home games against Real Sociedad, 1-2 in November 2022, although they have won just one of their last three.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإسباني لكرة القدم</category></programme><programme start="20241103172600" stop="20241103191800" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">Southampton vs Everton - English Premier League 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Southampton have won 13 Premier League home games against Everton – no side have they beaten more often on home soil in the competition. Though they’ve lost five of their last seven Premier League away games against Southampton, Everton won 2-1 on their last visit to St Mary’s in October 2022. They’ve not won consecutive away league games against Saints since January 1992.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإنجليزي الممتاز</category></programme><programme start="20241103173000" stop="20241103180000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Arabic Football - News</title><desc lang="ar">A special look at all the stories making the headlines in the world of Arabic Football. The many leagues across the MENA region and national Teams provide plenty of news stories .</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103174500" stop="20241103181500" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">La Liga Chronicles 2024/25 Ep.9</title><desc lang="ar">"A look back at the standout games from the most recent matchday, through extensive highlights and spectacularfootage."



































</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103174500" stop="20241103182000" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">Twente vs Chelsea - Mini Match - UEFA Women's Champions League 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Twente vs Chelsea - Extended Highlights - UEFA Women's Champions League 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">مباريات قصيرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103180000" stop="20241103190000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Nine O'Clock bulletin - NEWS</title><desc lang="ar">Latest news from the beIn SPORTS News room, previewing and reviewing developments and scores with contribution from around the world from beIN's reporters.</desc><category lang="ar">الأخبار الرياضية</category></programme><programme start="20241103181500" stop="20241103184500" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">La Liga World 2024/25 Ep.12</title><desc lang="ar"> A program of interviews and reports I  which all LALIGA clubs are represented  The program lasts 26 minutes and every week presents all the latest personal stories and the more human-interest side of the competition in a slow-paced and polished format.








































</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103182000" stop="20241103203000" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">USA vs RU30 - FIFA U17 Women's World Cup Dominican Rep. 2024 - 3rd Place Final</title><desc lang="ar">FIFA U17 Women's World Cup Dominican Rep. 2024 - 3rd Place Final</desc><category lang="ar">كأس العالم تحت 17 سنة</category></programme><programme start="20241103183000" stop="20241103203000" channel="10801"><title lang="ar">Final ATP 1000 Rolex Paris Masters 2024</title><desc lang="ar">The Rolex Paris Masters is the ninth and final ATP Masters 1000 event of the season. As the final tournament of the regular men’s tennis season, the Palais Omnisports in Bercy showcases the cream of the crop as players vie to win the prestigious title and clinch the remaining qualifying spots in the season-ending Nitto ATP Finals.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103183000" stop="20241103190000" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">Lille vs Lyon - Mini Match - French Ligue 1 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">Lille vs Lyon - Extended Highlights - French Ligue 1 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">مباريات قصيرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103184500" stop="20241103191500" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">Girona vs Leganes - Mini Match - La Liga 2024/2025</title><desc lang="ar">Girona vs Leganes - Extended Highlights - La Liga 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإسباني لكرة القدم</category></programme><programme start="20241103184500" stop="20241103203000" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Bayer Leverkusen vs Stuttgart - Bundesliga 2024/25 Week 9</title><desc lang="ar">VfB Stuttgart have won just one of their last 27 competitive meetings with Bayer 04 Leverkusen, a 1-0 Bundesliga away win in April 2018. Leverkusen are currently unbeaten in their last 13 games against VfB in all competitions  – a 14th game without defeat would be a first in this fixture. This is the fourth straight clash between the sides that has taken place in Leverkusen. VfB Stuttgart have led in each of their five competitive games against Bayer 04 Leverkusen under Sebastian Hoeneß, but they haven’t won any of them. The last three meetings have seen Leverkusen score after the 88-minute mark.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103190000" stop="20241103210000" channel="10802"><title lang="ar">Paris vs Toulouse - Marmara Spike ligue Volleyball 2024</title><desc lang="ar">The LNV Ligue A Masculine (LAM), currently known as the Marmara SpikeLigue for sponsorship reasons, is the top-tier men's volleyball league in France, established in 1938. Governed by the Ligue Nationale de Volley (LNV) under the French Volleyball Federation (FFVB), the league features France's elite volleyball talent. Formerly called Pro A until 2009, it shares a rich history and prestige akin to its basketball counterpart.

</desc><category lang="ar">الكرة الطائرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103190000" stop="20241103193500" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">PSG vs Lens - Mini Match - French Ligue 1 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">PSG vs Lens - Extended Highlights - French Ligue 1 2024/25</desc><category lang="ar">مباريات قصيرة</category></programme><programme start="20241103190000" stop="20241103191500" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Al Jawla  - Live Studio @23:00</title><desc lang="ar">Al Jawla covers the latest news and stories from sporting events across the planet. Including latest results and latest scores from the most recent games taking place. This daily look at the latest stories provides a fast paced update to sporting events.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103191500" stop="20241103193000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Stats - 3/11/24</title><desc lang="ar">An in depth look at the statistics that have emerged from the latest sporting events. All the data and facts for an even deeper understanding of the sporting world </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103191500" stop="20241103195500" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">LaLiga BEST 11 - Carlos Marchena</title><desc lang="ar">"Carlos Marchena played in defence for Valencia CF for 9 seasons. He won 5 trophies with Valencia CF, including two La Liga titles. He also played for Sevilla FC, Benfica, Villarreal CF and RC Deportivo. In La Liga he made a total of 330 appearances."








</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103191800" stop="20241103210000" channel="10402"><title lang="ar">Ipswich Town vs Leicester City -English Premier League 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Ipswich have won all three of their Premier League home games against Leicester – 4-1 in January 1995, 2-0 in January 2001 and 2-0 in December 2001. Leicester have lost just one of their last nine league games against Ipswich, with both meetings between the sides in the Championship last season finishing level.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإنجليزي الممتاز</category></programme><programme start="20241103193000" stop="20241103200000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">EPL Stories  2024/2025</title><desc lang="ar">Showcases the personalities who have shaped the Premier League era with a focus on the stories that resonate with international audiences.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103193000" stop="20241103200000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Bundesliga - Special 2024/2025 Best of October</title><desc lang="ar">October started with a top of the table thriller when Eintracht Frankfurt and Bayern München played out a dramatic match. After the latest international break, the Bundesliga returned with Bayern München taking on last years runners up VfB Stuttgart as they looked to defend top spot. Eintracht Frankfurt, spearheaded by Omar Mamoush in the form of his life, looked to keep up the chases under coach Dino Toppmüller. While Marco Rose's RB Leipzig continued their early season form, as did Xavi and Lois Openda, as they stayed neck and neck with Bayern München. There was many a stunning strike as the Bundesliga continued to provide goalscoring spectacle. We relive the footballing and emotional high</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103193000" stop="20241103213000" channel="10603"><title lang="ar">Boston Celtics vs Charlotte Hornets - NBA 2024 Regular Season</title><desc lang="ar">NBA 2024 Regular Season</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الأميركي لكرة السلة</category></programme><programme start="20241103193000" stop="20241103203000" channel="10601"><title lang="ar">Palestinian Football National Team - The other side of Resistance</title><desc lang="ar">After their perfect performance in the last Asian Cup QATAR 2023 , Palestinians Footballers are looking to improve more their presence in any international sports event including World Cup why not one day ? In this Documentary we are trying to understand what is the real situation in Palestine for those who are dreaming to leave and play in peace , what are their main opportunities to reach theirs Aims ? What is the Future they looking for ?        </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103193500" stop="20241103220000" channel="10602"><title lang="ar">Nantes vs Olympique Marseille - French Ligue 1 2024/25 Week 10</title><desc lang="ar">Nantes have not won any of their last eight games against Marseille in Ligue 1  and could equal their longest winless streak against OM in the top-flight. Nantes have not won any of their last six Ligue 1 matches  and could have their longest winless streak in the top-flight since February-May 2023.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الفرنسي</category></programme><programme start="20241103195500" stop="20241103220000" channel="10403"><title lang="ar">Athletic Bilbao vs Real Betis - LaLiga 2024/2025 Week 12</title><desc lang="ar">Athletic have lost three of their last five games against Real Betis in LaLiga, one more defeat than in their previous 16 matches against them in the competition. At home, Athletic have won nine of their last 10 games against Real Betis in LaLiga ; their most home wins against a single opponent in the competition since the 2013/14 season.
</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الإسباني لكرة القدم</category></programme><programme start="20241103200000" stop="20241103203000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">News Bulletin - @23:00</title><desc lang="ar">Latest news from the beIn SPORTS News room, previewing and reviewing developments and scores with contribution from around the world from beIN's reporters.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103200000" stop="20241103203000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">The Big Interview 2024/25</title><desc lang="ar">A chance to hear from one of the biggest and most interesting names in the Premier League in a more considered sit-down interview format. A thought-provoking 30-minute programme, the interviews will be detailed, topical and insightful.
























</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103203000" stop="20241103210000" channel="10304"><title lang="ar">Arabic Football - News</title><desc lang="ar">A special look at all the stories making the headlines in the world of Arabic Football. The many leagues across the MENA region and national Teams provide plenty of news stories .</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103203000" stop="20241103210000" channel="10404"><title lang="ar">Bundesliga - Special 2024/2025 Best of October</title><desc lang="ar">October started with a top of the table thriller when Eintracht Frankfurt and Bayern München played out a dramatic match. After the latest international break, the Bundesliga returned with Bayern München taking on last years runners up VfB Stuttgart as they looked to defend top spot. Eintracht Frankfurt, spearheaded by Omar Mamoush in the form of his life, looked to keep up the chases under coach Dino Toppmüller. While Marco Rose's RB Leipzig continued their early season form, as did Xavi and Lois Openda, as they stayed neck and neck with Bayern München. There was many a stunning strike as the Bundesliga continued to provide goalscoring spectacle. We relive the footballing and emotional high</desc><category lang="ar">الدوري الألماني لكرة اليد</category></programme><programme start="20241103203000" stop="20241103210000" channel="10401"><title lang="ar">UEFA UCL Magazine 2024/2025 - MD3 Review</title><desc lang="ar">A recap of the best of the action, plus a look forward to the next Match Day in Europe’s premium football competition, the UEFA Champions League. This season is the first in the new format, with 36 participating teams in a league phase replacing the previous Group stage. All matches from the UEFA Champions League are live and exclusive only on beIN.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103203000" stop="20241103210000" channel="10303"><title lang="ar">GKA Kite-Surf &amp; Hydrofoil Big Air World Cup - Sylt</title><desc lang="ar">Welcome to the northern German island of Sylt for a double-header of events on the Qatar Airways GKA Kite World Tour.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103203000" stop="20241103210000" channel="10601"><title lang="ar">AFC Asian Qualifiers 2024/25 - Best Goals MD3 &amp; MD4</title><desc lang="ar">The best goals from the third and fourth rounds of the Asian World Cup Qualifiers.</desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme><programme start="20241103203000" stop="20241103210000" channel="10801"><title lang="ar">Jannik Sinner vs Taylor Fritz - Men's Singles Final - Mini Matches - US Open 2024</title><desc lang="ar">Extended highlights of key matches from the US Open 2024 </desc><category lang="ar">الرياضة العام</category></programme></tv>